[
    {
        "question": "one",
        "answer": "odd"
    },
    {
        "question": "two",
        "answer": "even"
    },
    {
        "question": "three",
        "answer": "odd"
    },
    {
        "question": "four",
        "answer": "even"
    },
    {
        "question": "five",
        "answer": "odd"
    },
    {
        "question": "six",
        "answer": "even"
    },
    {
        "question": "seven",
        "answer": "odd"
    },
    {
        "question": "eight",
        "answer": "even"
    },
    {
        "question": "nine",
        "answer": "odd"
    },
    {
        "question": "ten",
        "answer": "even"
    },
    {
        "question": "eleven",
        "answer": "odd"
    },
    {
        "question": "twelve",
        "answer": "even"
    },
    {
        "question": "thirteen",
        "answer": "odd"
    }
]